Guide to the Robin Morgan Papers, 1940s-2019 and undated, bulk 1970-2019 RL.00913
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Teaching Materials Series, 1971-1998 and undated, bulk 1995-1997
  - University of Denver (Box T2)
    - Provost lunch speech, 1997 (Box T2)
    - Student papers, 1995-1997 (Box T2)
    - Women's Studies, 1996-1997 and undated (Box T2)
- Audio-Visual Materials Series, circa 1985-2001 and undated
  Contains cassette tapes with interviews that Morgan conducted with women in the Middle East during two visits in 1985 and 1989. There is also a recording of Morgan's reading of poems selected from A Hot January as well as a videotape titled, Saturday's Child; A Memoir. The collection is arranged by media type.
  [Originals closed to use. Use copies available in the collection. Please contact Research Services staff before coming to use the collection.]
  [Although the contents of the taped interviews are open to research, patrons are responsible for obtaining permission to publish from them.]
  - Cassette Tapes (Originals), circa 1985, 1989 and undated (Box AV1)
    - OR1. UNDP, circa 1985 (Box AV1)
    - OR2. UNDP, Gaza and the North circa 1985 (Box AV1)
    - OR3. Health center, Gaza, visits, circa 1985 (Box AV1)
    - OR4. Vienna brief, Gaza, circa 1985 (Box AV1)
    - OR5. Jerusalem, Giucamone, circa 1985 (Box AV1)
    - OR6. Settlements for women, Zahira Kamal, Palestinian women's work, circa 1985 (Box AV1)
    - OR7. Gaza - Health visits, Y. Barbary, circa 1985 (Box AV1)
    - OR8. Rita Giacaman, Ramallah, 1989 Jan. 14 (Box AV1)
    - OR9. End of Ibdn Haddi, Suha Eid, Jordan, circa 1985 (Box AV1)
    - OR10. Jordan, Haifa Bashur, Irbid, circa 1985 (Box AV1)
    - OR11. Jordan, Bag'A Camp, start of Haifa Bashur, circa 1985 (Box AV1)
    - OR12. Irbid, Suf camps, start of Ibdn Haddi, circa 1985 (Box AV1)
    - OR13. Village coop, Al Arrub camp, 1989 (Box AV1)
    - OR14. Jalazone camp, village coop, 1989 (Box AV1)
    - OR15. Gaza, circa 1985 (Box AV1)
    - OR16. Hayat Yaghi, Amman New camp, circa 1985 (Box AV1)
    - OR17. Ramallah Women's Teaching College, women's work, undated (Box AV1)
  - Videotapes
    - OR18. Women to Women: "Saturday's Child," 2001 Mar. (Box AV1)
  - Compact Discs
    - OR19.A Hot January, Selected Readings 1996-1999, 2000 (Box AV1)
  - Master and Use Copies (Box AV2)
    [Master copies are closed to general use.]
- Photographic and Visual Materials Series, circa 1974, 1982-1995 and undated
  This series includes 240 photographs and two painted portraits.
  - Photographic Materials, 1982-1995
    Consists of 240 photographs, 222 of which are color, and 18 black and white. Most of the images are snapshots from Morgan's trip to Egypt; the rest are pictures of Isel Rivero, and some taken by her. The photographs are arranged in their original order.
    - H Temple and Hathor temple, undated (Box PH1)
    - Valley of Kings and Queens, Hats., temples, goats, undated (Box PH1)
    - Nile, pyramids, Nawal, Sphinx, cat, undated (Box PH1)
    - N's country house and garden, Nile, undated (Box PH1)
    - N's village and chickens, relatives, children, undated (Box PH1)
    - Blake at Goodbye Pyramids, undated (Box PH1)
    - Bookshop, plane to Lufor, Fairy, Colossus, undated (Box PH1)
    - H Temple and Hathor temple, undated (Box PH1)
    - Miscellaneous photos, undated (Box PH1)
    - Isel Rivero
      - 1982, undated (Box PH1)
      - In Nicaragua, undated (Box PH1)
      - In Rwanda and Uganda, 1994-1995 and undated (Box PH1)
      - In Namibia, 1989-1990 and undated (Box PH1)
  - Visual Materials, circa 1974, undated
    This subseries includes two large painted portraits of Robin Morgan. One is a formal studio pose, painted on wood and depicting Morgan as a young woman during the time that she was a television and radio personality. The other was painted on canvas by Pat Mainardi (author of Politics of Housework) after Morgan achieved fame as a radical feminist activist and poet.
    - Portrait, by Pat Mainardi, oil on canvas, circa 1974 (Box PH1, Oversize-image 1: Please see catalog record for location.)
    - Portrait, formal studio pose, painted on wood, undated (Box PH1, Oversize-image 2: Please see catalog record for location.)
- Oversize Materials
  Contains materials from the Writings Series, the Subject Files Series, and the Speeches and Interviews Series. Poetry broadsides include the poem White Night, dedicated to Morgan and signed by Adrienne Rich. The Subject Files Subseries contains a complete set of issues of the feminist magazine Rat. Arranged alphabetically.
  - Writings Series (Box OS1)
    - Depth Perception Subseries
      - Copyright file -- Sojourner, 1978 Aug. (Box OS1)
    - Going Too Far Subseries
      - Reviews and adverts, 1977 (Box OS1)
    - A Hot January Subseries
      - Production, undated (Box OS1)
    - Lady of the Beasts Subseries
      - Reviews and adverts, 1976-1978 and undated (Box OS1)
    - Poems Subseries
      - Poems broadsides and awards, 1981-1982 (Box OS1)
  - Subject Files Series
    - International Feminist Activism and Resources Subseries
      - The Middle East -- General, 1980s (Box OS1)
    - U.S. Feminist Activism and Resources Subseries
      - Rat magazine, 1970s, 3 folders (Box OS1)
  - Speeches and Interviews Series
    - Announcements for speaking engagements, 1972-1992 and undated (Box OS1)
- Accession (2009-0069), 1993-2006, 3 boxes
  Addition (2009-0069) (900 items; 1.5 lin. ft.; 1993-2006) includes Morgan's files on sexual trafficking (2000); a master copy and page proofs of The Burning Time (2005-2006); and email printouts of responses to Letters from Ground Zero, which went viral on the Internet following Sept. 11, 2001.
  - Trafficking, 2000 (Box 1)
  - Conflitto e liberta femminile, Spring 1993 (Box 1)
  - The Burning Time drafts and master copy, 2005-2006 (Box 1)
  - Sept. 11, 2001 (Box 1)
  - Ghosts responses (Box 2)
  - Responses to Letters from Ground Zero (Box 2)
  - Loose correspondence (Box 2)
  - Loose correspondence (Box 3)
- Accession (2010-0176), 1947-2010, 19 boxes
  Accession (2010-0176) (18,450 items; 24.6 lin. ft.; dated 1947-2010) includes Morgan's travel files, correspondence, Ms. editorial files, and materials from her research and publications. General correspondence (dating 1996-2009) consists of email printouts and letters detailing Morgan's activities with various projects, conferences, and boards, including Equality Now and the February Sisters. It also includes her thoughts on the 2008 presidential election, including a re-written version of Goodbye to All That discussing the Hillary Clinton campaign.
  The Ms. files (dating 2002-2010) include global dispatches, correspondence, and cover story interviews by Morgan of Madeleine Albright and Jane Fonda. This section also contains files from the Ms. search for editor-in-chief.
  A large portion of the accession relates to Morgan's writings, poetry, and published books. These materials consist of drafts, correspondence with publishers, publicity and press, reader reactions, reviews of her work, and rights permissions. Works represented include Monster, which included the poem Arraignment; The Mysteries, a play; Upstairs in the Garden; Going Too Far; The Anatomy of Freedom; The Witch Tales; Sisterhood is Forever; and other poems and articles. The majority of the Sisterhood is Forever materials are contributor files, including women like Gloria Steinem, Eleanor Smeal, Eve Ensler, Rep. Eleanor Holmes Norton, and many others.
  Also represented are supporting materials, mainly clippings and other miscellaneous items, from Morgan's childhood, adolescence, and early adulthood that she used for writing her Memoirs. These clippings include coverage of her activities as a child star on the television show Mama, as well as her other performances, radio and television shows, and modelling engagements. Morgan's early activities in the women's liberation movement are also represented in these clippings, such as her protesting the Miss America competition in 1969 and coverage of her book, Sisterhood Is Powerful. The original clippings are extremely fragile and may require Technical Services intervention.
  Other materials in the accession include various research and project files, many supporting Morgan's activities or writings. For example, there is a series of folders on clitoredectomy and female genital mutilation, culminating in a draft prepared by Morgan and Gloria Steinem of an article published in the 1970s. Materials from the Women's Media Center are closed due to restrictions. There is also a significant amount of audiovisual material, including film, VHS, reel-to-reel audio, and DVDs. These will require reformatting prior to use by researchers.
  - Travel, 1959-2001 (Box 1)
    - London, Paris, Florence, 1959 (2 folders) (Box 1)
    - UN women's conferences, Copenhagen and Oslo, 1980-1981 (2 folders) (Box 1)
    - Mexico, 1981 (Box 1)
    - UN panel, Vienna, 1982 (Box 1)
    - London Book Fair, 1984 (Box 1)
    - Meetings with Greek women, Greece, 1984 (Box 1)
    - Holiday, St. Thomas, 1984-1985 (Box 1)
    - CEDAW meetings, Brazil, 1987 (Box 1)
    - Japan, 1988 (Box 1)
    - Occupied Territories, 1989 (Box 1)
    - Asia Foundation work with women, Nepal, 1994 (4 folders) (Box 1)
    - UN women's conference, Beijing, 1995 (3 folders) (Box 1)
    - General clippings, China, 1995 (Box 1)
    - Book tour, Italy, 1996 (Box 1)
    - Nepal, 1997 (Box 1)
    - Women's conference, Basque Country, Spain, 1998 (Box 1)
    - Book tour, Italy, 1998 (Box 1)
    - Book tour, Italy, 2001 (Box 1)
  - Ms. materials (Box 2)
    - Search for editor-in-chief, 2002 (2 folders) (Box 2)
    - Interim/summer issues, 2002 (9 folders) (Box 2)
    - Correspondence, 2003 (3 folders) (Box 2)
    - Columns, 2003 (2 folders) (Box 2)
    - Correspondence, 2004 (Box 2)
    - Los Angeles trip, 2004 (Box 2)
    - Columns, 2004 (Box 2)
    - Global/international, 2004 (2 folders) (Box 2)
    - International rejects, 2004 (3 folders) (Box 2)
    - Dispatches and networking, Winter 2004 (Box 2)
    - Albright interview, 2003-2004 (Box 3)
    - News, Winter 2004 (Box 3)
    - Spring 2005 (Box 3)
    - Global news, Spring 2005 (Box 3)
    - Summer 2005 (Box 3)
    - Dispatches, Summer 2005 (Box 3)
    - Jane Fonda cover story, 2005 (Box 3)
    - Global, Fall 2005 (Box 3)
    - Dispatches, Fall 2005 (Box 3)
    - 2005 (2 folders) (Box 3)
    - Global news, Winter 2005-2006 (Box 3)
    - Dispatches, Winter 2005-2006 (Box 3)
    - Dispatches, Spring 2006 (Box 3)
    - Global news, Spring 2006 (Box 3)
    - Global, Summer 2006 (Box 3)
    - Global, Fall 2006 (Box 3)
    - Winter 2006-2007 (Box 3)
    - Global, Spring 2007 (Box 3)
    - Global, Summer 2007 (Box 3)
    - Fall 2007 (Box 4)
    - Winter 2008 (Box 4)
    - Summer 2008 (Box 4)
    - Global, Fall 2008 (Box 4)
    - Winter 2008-2009 (Box 4)
    - Global, Spring 2009 (Box 4)
    - Summer 2009 (Box 4)
    - Global, Fall 2009 (Box 4)
    - Winter 2010 (2 folders) (Box 4)
    - Spring 2010 (Box 4)
    - Summer 2010 (Box 4)
    - Fall 2010 (Box 4)
  - Women's Radio Network, 2005 (2 folders) (Box 4)
  - University of Denver, 2002-2005 (2 folders) (Box 5)
  - General correspondence, 1986-2009
    - Bella Abzug, 1986 (Box 5)
    - 1996 (Box 5)
    - 1999 (2 folders) (Box 5)
    - 2000 (3 folders) (Box 5)
    - 2001 (5 folders) (Box 5)
    - 2001-2002 (Box 5)
    - 2002 (4 folders) (Box 5)
    - 2002 (2 folders) (Box 6)
    - Equality Now, 2002 (Box 6)
    - February Sisters, 2002 (Box 6)
    - 2003 (6 folders) (Box 6)
    - 2004 (Box 6)
    - Equality Now, 2004 (Box 6)
    - 2005 (Box 6)
    - 2005 (3 folders) (Box 7)
    - 2006 (4 folders) (Box 7)
    - 2007 (4 folders) (Box 7)
    - 2008 (3 folders) (Box 7)
    - 2009 (Box 7)
  - Beijing UN Conference piece, 1995 (Box 8)
  - Correspondence re: Women's Studies Encyclopedia, 1992-2000 (Box 8)
  - Global Fund for Women, 1990-1999 (4 folders) (Box 8)
  - Feminist Press Board, 1996-1998 (Box 8)
  - Rat, women's takeover issue, February 1970 (Box 8)
    Includes Goodbye to All That (number 1).
  - Bella Abzug's death and memorial service file, 1998 (Box 8)
  - Bella Awards copy, 2001 (Box 8)
  - Bella Book (The Bella Project), 2004 (Box 8)
  - Gil Morgenstern gigs, 2008-2009 (Box 8)
  - Chai Ling Ms. interview (re: Tiananmen Square), 1989-1990 (Box 8)
  - BBC Byline, 1990-1991 (Box 8)
  - Song lyrics, undated (Box 8)
  - Monster files, 1968-1979 (Box 8)
    Materials from Morgan's first book of poetry (1972). Includes draft, submissions, correspondence, the Feminist Art Journal and other feminist editions, reactions, and reviews. Contains discussion of the Ted Hughes/Sylvia Plath controversy.
  - Vietnamese poetry translations, 1967-1968 (2 folders) (Box 9)
  - Poems: translations, 1981 (Box 9)
  - Poems set to music, 1967-1975 (Box 9)
  - The Mysteries (Box 9)
  - Upstairs in the Garden, 1989-1991 (7 folders) (Box 9)
    Literary magazine published poems, contracts, discarded poems, production, reviews, and reactions.
  - Poems: magazine submissions and publications, 1974-1981 (3 folders) (Box 9)
  - A Garden Journal, 2000-2002 (3 folders) (Box 9)
  - Essays and articles, 1977 (2 folders) (Box 9)
  - The Handmaiden of the Holy Man, 2003 (Box 9)
  - Fundamentalisms re: religions, 1996-1997 (8 folders) (Box 9)
  - Going Too Far, 1969-1976 (4 folders) (Box 10)
    Includes drafts, production materials, correspondence, etc.
  - Monster and Going Too Far contracts and royalty statements, 1971-1980 (Box 10)
  - Permissions: articles and poems, 1976-1994 (5 folders) (Box 10)
  - Infringements and plagiarisms, 1973-1981 (Box 10)
  - The Witch Tales drafts, undated (3 folders) (Box 10)
  - The Anatomy of Freedom, 1981-1986 (9 folders) (Box 10)
    Manuscripts, drafts, publication, reviews, and reactions.
  - The Anatomy of Freedom publication rights, 1982-1999 (Box 11)
  - Depth Perception, 1982 (Box 11)
  - The Word of a Woman, 1990s (10 folders) (Box 11)
  - Dry Your Smile, 1987-1988 (Box 11)
  - Memoir materials
    Press coverage and other materials from Morgan's entertainment career (as a child in the 1950s), her activism during the Women's Liberation movement (1970s-present), and her writings and public events. Most of the newspaper clippings are extremely fragile and may require preservation photocopies to be made before use. Please handle with care.
    - Childhood clippings and correspondence, 1947-1950 (Box 11)
    - Childhood scrapbook pages, 1947-1950 (Box 11)
    - Mama clippings and press (3 folders) (Box 11)
    - Television shows, books, and miscellaneous clippings, 1951-1980 (Box 11)
    - Teen years clippings (Box 11)
    - Schoolwork (Box 11)
    - Women's Liberation clippings, 1960s-1970s (2 folders) (Box 11)
      Including Miss America coverage, Sisterhood is Powerful, and interviews with Morgan.
    - General press clippings, 1980s-1990s (Box 11)
  - Memoir materials: Women's Liberation movement clippings, 1960s-1970s (2 folders) (Box 12)
  - Clitoredectomy (female genital mutilation) files, 1970s (4 folders) (Box 12)
    Includes drafts from piece on female circumcision by Gloria Steinem and Robin Morgan.
  - Katharine Hepburn research file, 1981 and undated (Box 12)
  - Poems: translations, 1981 (Box 12)
  - Audiovisual materials (Box 13)
    Consists of 10 VHS tapes, 9 audio cassette tapes, 16 reel-to-reels, 1 film reel, and 2 DVDs. Includes video clips from Morgan's child modeling and clips and reviews of her television shows, including Mama and other plays. Audio tapes include Their Own Country (a verse play), Church of the Ascension, Fifth Avenue, New York, 1961; Mike Wallace interview with Morgan; and her teenage trip abroad in the 1950s. Audio cassettes include tapes of Morgan's interview with Madeleine Albright and her leading the women's takeover of the Phil Donahue Show. Videotapes and DVDs include the Bella Abzug memorial service, with speakers Morgan, Gloria Steinem, Jane Fonda, Shirley Maclaine, Marlo Thomas, etc.; Morgan's interview on Charlie Rose; film of the first Miss America Pageant protest, 1968; and Morgan's participation on various panels.
    - Miss America, 2001; 1:39:08 (Box 13, Video-cassette RL00913-VHS-0001, Digital-materials RL00913-SET-0001, Video-file RL00913-VHS-0001.mkv)
      Scope and Contents
      A history of the Miss America pageant, produced for American Experience by Clio Inc. and Orchard Film Productions.
  - Sisterhood is Forever files, 2000-2003 (Box 14)
    - Kathy Boudin and Roslyn Smith correspondence (4 folders) (Box 14)
    - General correspondence, 2001 (Box 14)
    - Publishing/contributor files, A-B, 2001-2003
      - Bravo, Ellen (Box 14)
      - Appel-Bronstein, Ellen (Box 14)
      - Angier, Natalie (Box 14)
      - Adler, Margot (Box 14)
      - Adams, Carol J. (Box 14)
      - Acosta-Belén, Edna, and Christine E. Bose (Box 14)
    - Events (5 folders) (Box 14)
    - First serial, 2002-2003 (Box 14)
    - Revised versions (Box 14)
    - Bids and contracts (Box 14)
    - Conference, 2002 (Box 14)
    - Book and manuscript, 2003 (Box 14)
    - Random House correspondence, 2002 (Box 14)
    - Contributor contracts, Random House (2 folders) (Box 14)
    - WSP contracts (Box 14)
    - Reviews, 2003 (2 folders) (Box 14)
    - Reactions, 2003 (Box 14)
    - Foreign rights, 2002-2003 (Box 14)
    - Film/television rights, 2004 (Box 14)
    - Promotion, 2002-2003 (2 folders) (Box 14)
    - Production, 2002 (2 folders) (Box 14)
    - Publishing/contributor files, C-M, 2001-2003 (Box 15)
      - Carter, Vednita (Box 15)
      - Chavkin, Wendy (Box 15)
      - Crenshaw, Kimberlé (2 folders) (Box 15)
      - DiPerna, Paula (Box 15)
      - Drusine, Helen (Box 15)
      - Dworkin, Andrea (Box 15)
      - Ensler, Eve (Box 15)
      - Findlen, Barbara (Box 15)
      - Funiciello, Theresa (Box 15)
      - Guy-Sheftall, Beverly (Box 15)
      - Gilligan, Carol (Box 15)
      - Gould, Sara K. (Box 15)
      - Guerilla Girls (Box 15)
      - Hanna, Kathleen (Box 15)
      - Hershey, Laura (Box 15)
      - Hill, Anita (Box 15)
      - Howe, Florence (Box 15)
      - Hughes, Donna (Box 15)
      - Jay, Karla (Box 15)
      - Jemison, Mae C. (Box 15)
      - Jenkins, Carol (Box 15)
      - Kennedy, Claudia (Box 15)
      - Kessler-Harris, Alice (Box 15)
      - Kidwell, Clara Sue (Box 15)
      - Kissling, Frances (Box 15)
      - Levine, Suzanne Braun (Box 15)
      - Macdonald, Barbara (Box 15)
      - MacKinnon, Catherine (Box 15)
      - Martin, Jane Roland (Box 15)
      - Michals, Debra (Box 15)
      - Morgan, Robin (3 folders) (Box 15)
    - Publishing/contributor files, N-Z, 2001-2003 (Box 16)
      - Neuwirth, Jessica (Box 16)
      - New Moon Girls (Box 16)
      - Norsigian, Judy (OBOS) (Box 16)
      - Norton, Eleanor Holmes (Box 16)
      - Paley, Grace (Box 16)
      - Richards, Amy, and Marianne Schnall (Box 16)
      - Richards, Cecile (Box 16)
      - Sachs, Carolyn (Box 16)
      - Schroeder, Pat (Box 16)
      - Smeal, Eleanor (Box 16)
      - Steinem, Gloria (Box 16)
      - Thom, Mary (2 folders) (Box 16)
      - Victoria, Jasmine (Box 16)
      - Wattleton, Faye (Box 16)
      - Wilson, Marie (Box 16)
      - Zia, Helen (Box 16)
  - Women's Media Center files (Box 17-19)
    These boxes are CLOSED due to RESTRICTIONS.
- Accession (2015-0060), 1968-2014, 14 boxes
  Accession (2015-0060)(4050 items; 5.4 lin. ft.; dated 1968-2014); includes additions to Morgan's personal and professional papers. These include Morgan's general correspondence and correspondence with Marilyn Waring, copies of Ms. Magazine, Morgan's writing and appearances, interviews, and records of the Women's Media Center.
  Conditions Governing Access
  The contents of boxes 8-9, 11-12, and 16 are currently closed to use due to restrictions. Researchers may contact Rubenstein Library staff for further information.
  - Ms. Magazine issues, 2012-2013 (Box 1)
  - Ms. Magazine issues, 2010-2012 (Box 2)
  - Correspondence, 2010-2013 (8 folders) (Box 3)
  - Nawal visit, 2011 (Box 3)
  - Ms. Iron Lung, 2012 (Box 3)
  - Ms. Magzine, Winter 2013-2014 (Box 3)
  - Correspondence, 2013 (Box 4)
  - Pat Mitchell and Makers, 2013 (Box 4)
  - The Yarner drafts and notes, 2012 (Box 5)
  - The Word Worker drafts and notes, 2012 (Box 5)
  - The House draft, undated (Box 5)
  - Correspondence, 2008-2009 (Box 6)
  - The Yarner drafts, master copy, and notes, undated (Box 6)
  - Women's Media Center records, 2010-2014 (Box 8-9)
    Materials in these boxes are closed to use.
  - Robin Morgan/Marilyn Waring correspondence, 1986-1992 (Box 11-12)
  - RM New Zealand letters, 1993-1994 (Box 13)
  - New Zealand Book Festival, 1993-1994 (Box 13)
  - Correspondence, 2014 (Box 13)
  - President Carter, 2014 (Box 13)
  - UN Conference on Women, 1995 (Box 13)
  - Unspinning preface, 2013 (Box 14)
  - Fever Zone Journal, 1995-1986 (Box 14)
  - Marilyn Waring writings, 1985-1989 (Box 14)
  - Marilyn Waring clips and bios, 1981-1991 (Box 15)
  - Ms. Magazine, Fall and Spring, 2014 (Box 15)
  - Miss America protest ephemera, 1968 (Box 15)
  - Our Bodies, Our Selves, (RM's copy) 1971 (Box 15)
  - Protest buttons (Box 15)
  - Robin Morgan/Marilyn Waring correspondence, 1985-1995 (Box 16)
    Materials in this box are closed to use.
- Accession (2016-0176), 2012-2016
  Contains Women's Media Center materials, correspondence, and books.
  Women's Media Center materials closed by donor request.
  - Women's Media Center Live (WMCL), 2012-2016
    - 2012
      - Episode 1, 2012-08-26 (Box 1)
      - Episode 2, 2012-09-02 (Box 1)
      - Episode 3, 2012-09-09 (Box 1)
      - Episode 4, 2012-09-16 (Box 1)
      - Episode 5, 2012-09-23 (Box 1)
      - Episode 6, 2012-09-29 (Box 1)
      - Episode 7, 2012-10-06 (Box 1)
      - Episode 8, 2012-10-13 (Box 1)
      - Episode 9, 2012-10-20 (Box 1)
      - Episode 10, 2012-10-27 (Box 1)
      - Episode 11, 2012-11-03 (Box 1)
      - Episode 12, 2012-11-10 (Box 1)
      - Episode 13, 2012-11-17 (Box 1)
      - Episode 14, 2012-11-24 (Box 1)
      - Episode 15, 2012-12-01 (Box 1)
      - Episode 16, 2012-12-08 (Box 1)
      - Episode 17, 2012-12-15 (Box 1)
      - Episode 18, 2012-12-22 (Box 1)
      - Episode 19, 2012-12-29 (Box 1)
    - 2013
      - Episode 20, 2013-01-05 (Box 1)
      - Episode 21, 2013-01-12 (Box 1)
      - Episode 22, 2013-01-19 (Box 1)
      - Episode 23, 2013-01-26 (Box 1)
      - Episode 24, 2013-02-02 (Box 1)
      - Episode 25, 2013-02-09 (Box 1)
      - Episode 26, 2013-02-16 (Box 1)
      - Episode 27, 2013-02-23 (Box 1)
      - Episode 28, 2013-03-01 (Box 1)
      - Episode 29, 2013-03-13 (Box 1)
      - Episode 30, 2013-03-16 (Box 1)
      - Episode 31, 2013-03-23 (Box 1)
      - Episode 32, 2013-03-30 (Box 1)
      - Episode 33, 2013-04-06 (Box 1)
      - Episode 34, 2013-04-13 (Box 1)
      - Episode 35, 2013-04-20 (Box 1)
      - Episode 36, 2013-04-27 (Box 1)
      - Episode 37, 2013-05-04 (Box 1)
      - Episode 38, 2013-05-11 (Box 1)
      - Episode 39, 2013-05-18 (Box 1)
      - Episode 40, 2013-05-25 (Box 1)
      - Episode 41, 2013-06-01 (Box 1)
      - Episode 42, 2013-06-08 (Box 1)
      - Episode 43, 2013-06-15 (Box 1)
      - Episode 44, 2013-06-22 (Box 1)
      - Episode 45, 2013-06-29 (Box 1)
      - Episode 46, 2013-07-06 (Box 1)
      - Episode 47, 2013-07-13 (Box 1)
      - Episode 48, 2013-07-20 (Box 1)
      - Episode 49, 2013-07-27 (Box 1)
      - Episode 50, 2013-09-07 (Box 1)
      - Episode 51, 2013-09-14 (Box 1)
      - Episode 52, 2013-09-21 (Box 1)
      - Episode 53, 2013-09-28 (Box 1)
      - Episode 54, 2013-10-05 (Box 2)
      - Episode 55, 2013-10-12 (Box 2)
      - Episode 56, 2013-10-19 (Box 2)
      - Episode 57, 2013-10-26 (Box 2)
      - Episode 58, 2013-11-02 (Box 2)
      - Episode 59, 2013-11-09 (Box 2)
      - Episode 60, 2013-11-16 (Box 2)
      - Episode 61, 2013-11-23 (Box 2)